무슨 일인데요?
What do you want?
페니한테는 별로 놀랍지도 않겠지만
I'm certain this will come as no surprise to you,
레너드가 이번에도 깨질 것 같아요
but Leonard is failing in yet another relationship.
스테파니랑 문제 있어요?
He's having problems with Stephanie?
스테파니는 인터넷에서 아무 남자한테나 가상 가축을 보내고 있어요
She's sending virtual livestock to random men on the Internet.
둘을 계속 엮으려면 자료가 필요해요
If I have any hope of keeping them together, I need data.
레너드가 한 짓을 빼놓지 말고 말해요
Specifically, I need to know exactly what Leonard did
레너드가 무슨 짓을 해서 페니의 꼭지를 돌게 했었는지
that caused you to pop an emotional cap in his buttocks.
네? - 속어잖아요
What? - Again, urban slang.
제가 봐도 꽤 유창하게 쓰는 것 같네요
In which, I believe I'm gaining remarkable fluency.